♪ Oh, what fun it is to ride ♪
♪ In a one-horse
open sleigh, hey! ♪
(Raj:)Mmm. Amy,
(Raj:)that pudding was delicious.
(Sheldon:)If you like raisins.
(Amy:)Thank you. And it's figs.
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)Oh, in that case,
it was pretty good.
(Bernadette:)You feeling okay? You hardly
touched your goose.
(Howard:)It smelled too much
like blue jay.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Can I help you
clean up?
(Amy:)Oh, you Heimliched a ball
of wool out of me; you're good.
(Sheldon:)Uh, what do you say
we exchange gifts?
(Penny:)Oh, Sheldon,
we didn't bring any.
(Leonard:)I thought you hate
giving gifts.
(Howard:)Yeah, I do.
(Sheldon:)Which is why I got Amy this.
(Amy:)You got me something?
(Sheldon:)Oh, not just
something, no.
(Sheldon:)It's from the heart,
it's holiday-themed,
(Sheldon:)and I swallowed the gift receipt
so you cannot return it.
(Amy:)Look at you on Santa's lap.
(Amy:)That's so sweet.